RESUME

PERSONAL DETAILS

NAME : NurSyazwani Diyana Binti Ahmad

IC NUMBER : 920824-02-6214

ADDRESS : 19, Felda Teloi Kanan

09300 Kuala Ketil

Kedah

TEL (HOME) : 04-4192602 **TEL (MOBILE)** : 013-4704057

MARITAL STATUS : Single

EMAIL : nursyazwanidiyana@yahoo.com



CAREER OBJECTIVE

To build a career in Management field and contribute my knowledge, skills and competencies gained in related field. Moreover, I want to be employed and experienced in a progressive and innovative work environment that will fully utilize my current skills with opportunities for advancement.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Bachelor in Business Administration (Hons) Marketing Management

Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Pulau Pinang

CGPA: 3.46

MARCH 2014-JAN 2017

Diploma in International Business

Politeknik Melaka, Melaka (PMK)

CGPA: 3.60

JUNE 2010-DEC 2012

SKILL AND CAPABILITIES

1) LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

LANGUAGESPOKENWRITTENMalayExcellentExcellentEnglishGoodGood

2) COMPUTER APPLICATION

Extensive Experience With Microsoft Office Word, Excell, Power Point

WORKING EXPERIENCES

INDUSTRIAL TRAINING AT PLEXUS MANUFACTURING (ISLANDVIEW) SDN. BHD. (JULY 2016 - NOV 2016 / 4 MONTHS)

- Hiring process: Involve with the activities in the process of hiring new employees for example deal with the working agency and set up the interview session. Moreover, process is also involve with the training and orientation time.
- P-file Management: Arrange files according employees number in order to easy look up and space saving.
- Locker & Key Management: Involve with the locker and key arrangement given to new hire employees.
- Canteen Management: Deal with the canteen workers regarding any issues arrive such as the meeting schedule, price listing and menu at canteen.
- Transport & Overtime Management: Arrange transport report and schedule for transporter due to effectiveness and arrangement of food with the canteen regarding total workers on duty.
- Key in employee's data in Workday System: Accuracy is needed in order to key in data in system to easy access and to minimize error.

ACCOUNT CLERK AT KILANG BIHUN BERSATU SDN BHD (KBB)

- Key in data in UBS accounting system regarding the customers' order.
- Print Purchase Order / Debit Note / Credit Note referring to salesman note.
- Handle salesman's sales account. Balancing is very needed in order to organized the account. All payment need to be settle and updated to salesman for them to take further action.

INDUSTRIAL TRAINING AT FELDA RUBBER INDUSTRIES SDN BHD TELOI KANAN (FRISB) (DEC 2010 - JUNE 2011 / 6 MONTHS)

- Key in employees' data in SAP system, regarding their leave and others.
- Manage documents in office to make sure the organization is perfect and can easy access to it.
- Manage customers problem in office and deal with workers and other agency about payment due to their services.

PERSONAL ACHIEVEMENTS

Anugerah Pingat Ketua Jabatan Perdagangan (Semester 2 – 6)

Treasurer Of Commerce Department (Semester 3)

2011 - 2013

Bachelor of Business Administration (Hons) Marketing Dean's Award

2014 & 2016

PARTICIPANT: Grads Sales Day event at MYDIN Bertam, Penang 2015

Faculty of Business Management (Marketing)

Able to develop skills on how to promote products and attract customers

to purchase.

FACILITATOR: "Consumer Trend Canvas" Creative & Innovative 2015

Sharing Session

Faculty of Business Management (Marketing)

PROMOTION COMMITTEE: "Young Entrepreneurs Journey"

2015

event at MYDIN Bertam, Penang

Faculty of Business Management (Marketing)

Able to develop skills how to promote products and attract customers to purchase.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Strength: Enthusiastic, initiative, creative, innovative, curiosity, team player, hard worker, problem solver, adaptive, responsible.

I am energetic and enthusiastic with aims to succeed and committed in any work assignment.

I am looking forward for a job that is challenging in terms of skills and knowledge that can help me in gaining new experience and understanding especially sharpening my leadership skills.

I am well motivated, can be a good leader or follower, and enjoying meeting people and dealing with them.

Willing to travel : 100%
Willing to relocate : Yes
Possess own transport : Yes

REFEREES

NAME : Aliza Binti Mohd Razali

TELEPHONE NUMBER : 013-4098961

POSITION : Section Head of Human Resource Management Plexus

Manufacturing (Islandview) Sdn. Bhd.

ORGANIZATION: Plexus Manufacturing (Islandview) Sdn. Bhd.

NAME : Nor Aminin Binti Khalid

TELEPHONE NUMBER : 019-4468858

POSITION: Lecturer of Faculty Business Management

Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Pulau Pinang

ORGANIZATION : Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Pulau Pinang